Guide to the Administrative Papers of Chancellor George Bugliarello RG.007
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series IV: Polytechnic
  - Subseries B: Center for Technology in Merchandising (CTM)
    - Proposal – Draft, 1997 December 4 (Box 43, Folder 39)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation - Annual Report, 1999 September-October, 2000 October (Box 43, Folder 40)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation - Miscellaneous, 1998 May - 2002 November (Box 43, Folder 41)
    - Symbol – Grant Payments, 1999 January - 2001 April (Box 43, Folder 42)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation – Final Report, 2004 June-July (Box 43, Folder 43)
    - Federated Logistics & Operations – Funding, 2001 March, 2004 June (Box 43, Folder 44)
    - E-Commerce and New Business Models Seminar – December 13, 1999, 1999 November-December (Box 43, Folder 45)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation Grant – Miscellaneous, 1998 April - 1999 April (Box 43, Folder 46)
    - National Science Foundation Grant Proposal, 2001 August (Box 43, Folder 47)
    - Miscellaneous, 2001 January-August (Box 43, Folder 48)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation - Proposal, 1998 April (Box 43, Folder 49)
    - Federated Department Stores Foundation – Donation, 2001 February - 2004 August, Undated (Box 43, Folder 50)
    - Follow up / Status report – Student presentations, 2002 December - 2003 January (Box 43, Folder 51)
    - Sears Roebuck & Co. Grant, 1999 July - 2000 March (Box 43, Folder 52)
    - MOTIR – Miscellaneous, 2000 November - 2003 April, Undated (Box 43, Folder 53)
    - Policy Board Members – Correspondence, 2003 March 10 (Box 43, Folder 54)
    - Policy Board – Meetings, 2001 June - 2004 September (Box 43, Folder 55)
    - Request for Official Designation as Center for Technology in Supply Chains and Merchandising, 2002 October-November (Box 43, Folder 56)
    - Workshop Proceedings, 1998 February, March (Box 43, Folder 57)
    - Ewing Marion Kauffman Foundation, 2004 March-May (Box 43, Folder 58)
    - Policy Board Meeting, 2001 September 27 (Box 43, Folder 59)
    - Michael Greenstein, 2002 August 29 (Box 43, Folder 60)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 1996 August - 1997 February (Box 43, Folder 61)
    - "A Program in Technology and Merchandising at Polytechnic University" - Early Draft, 1995 September 13 (Box 43, Folder 62)
    - Book Mailing, 1998 March-April (Box 43, Folder 63)
    - Workshop of Executives in the Merchandising and Distribution Sectors - Correspondence, 1997 May (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Workshop Program - Follow Up, 1997 June-July (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1997 August-November (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Meeting with A. Martinez, J. Swartz and President Chang, 1997 February 14 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 July - 1998 June, 2002 September, Undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 1996 August - 1998 May (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Meeting - A. Martinez and President Chang, 1998 March 3 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Subseries C: Leadership Seminar Series, 1994-1996
    - Joseph Jacobs - Speaker - October 17, 1994, 1994 September-October (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Clifford Goldsmith - Speaker - October 24, 1994, 1994 October-November (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Stewart G. Nagler - Speaker - November 14, 1994, 1994 October (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Horwitch, Mel - Speaker - January 29, 1995, 1995 January 29 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Donald M. Cox - Speaker - January 30, 1995, 1995 January-February (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Eleanor Baum - Speaker - February 5, 1995, 1995 February 5 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Casimir Skrzypczak - Speaker - February 6, 1995, 1994 July - 1995 February (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Bill Friend - Speaker - February 10, 1995, 1995 January (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Leonard Berkowitz - Speaker - February 19, 1995, 1995 February 19 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Georgia Fisanick - Speaker - February 20, 1995, 1994 October - 1995 February (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Steve Wallach - Speaker - February 27, 1995, 1995 January-February (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - John G. Puente - Speaker - March 6, 1994, 1994 October - 1994 January (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Herman Fialkov - Speaker - March 13, 1995, 1994 October - 1995 April (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Richard W. Foxen - Speaker - March 20, 1995, 1995 March-April (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - David Dibner - Speaker - March 27, 1995, 1994 November - 1995 March (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Peter M. Lehrer - Speaker - April 3, 1995, 1995 March-April (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Dr. Harry C. Wechsler - Speaker - April 17, 1995, 1995 February-April (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Arthur C. Martinez - Speaker - April 17, 1995, 1995 January (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Steve Greenfield - Speaker - April 24, 1995, 1995 March-May (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Henry J. Singer - Speaker - April 26, 1995, 1995 January-April (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - David A. Conklin - Speaker - October 2, 1995, 1995 September-November (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Eugene J. Fasullo - Speaker - October 9, 1995, 1995 August-December (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Paul Soros - Speaker - October 23, 1995, 1995 September-November (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Irene Van Slyke - Speaker - October 30, 1995, 1995 October (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - John Mayo - Speaker - November 6, 1995, 1995 September-December (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - Senator Frank Padavan - Speaker - November 13, 1995, 1995 September-December (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - Robert Dalziel - Speaker - November 27, 1995, 1995 September-November (Box 44, Folder 34)
    - Invitations to Speakers, 1994 September - 1995 January (Box 44, Folder 35)
    - Seminar Refreshments - Invoice, 1995 January-February (Box 44, Folder 36)
    - Student Registration Forms - RESTRICT, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 37)
    - Sign-in Sheet, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 38)
    - Sign-In Sheets - RESTRICT, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 39)
    - Thank You Notes, 1995 May (Box 44, Folder 40)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994 August - 1995 September (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - Subseries D: Professional Calendars
    - Professional Calendar, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 42)
    - Professional Calendar, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 43)
    - Professional Calendar, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 44)
    - Professional Calendar, 2004 (Box 44, Folder 45)
    - Professional Calendar, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 46)
    - Professional Calendar - Miscellaneous Inserts, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 47)
    - Professional Calendar - Grant Budget Status Reports, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Professional Calendar, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Professional Calendar - Miscellaneous Inserts, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Professional Calendar, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Professional Calendar, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Professional Calendar - Miscellaneous Inserts, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Professional Calendar, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Professional Calendar - Miscellaneous Inserts, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Professional Calendar, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Professional Calendar, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Professional Calendar, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Professional Calendar - Miscellaneous Inserts, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Professional Calendar, 2011 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Professional Calendar, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Professional Calendar, 2006 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Professional Calendar - Miscellaneous Inserts, 2006 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Professional Calendar, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Professional Calendar, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Professional Calendar, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Professional Calendar, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Professional Calendar, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Professional Calendar, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Suberies E: Urban Sustainability
    - "A Major Workshop on Engineering Education for Urban Sustainability", 2004 October-November (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Compliments to Sustainability Class – Notes, Clippings, 2009-2010 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Notes, Undated (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - "Integrated Interdisciplinary Program on Urban Sustainability", 2003 July 16 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - The Sustainable Mobility Project – Full Report – World Business Council for Sustainable Development, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Mobility 2001 – World Business Council for Sustainable Development (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - The Sustainable Mobility Project – Progress Report, 2002 July (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - "Sustainable Habitats" – NRC Grant, 1995-1996 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Urban Sustainability Center, 2004 September (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Center on Emerging Urban Challenges – Presentation, Undated (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - Sustainability Practices Committee – Polytechnic University, 2008 March-September (Box 45, Folder 33)
    - Urban Systems Group – Polytechnic University, 2006 September-October (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Roberta E. Weisbrod – Partnership for Sustainable Ports, 2009 May-June (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Sustainability Leadership Certificate – Robert N. Ubell, 2009 March-July (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Jim O'Grady – Center for an Urban Future, 2007 May 24 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Urban Security: Engineering the Protection of Our Cities, Volume 1 – Conference Proceedings, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Bruce Niswander, 2007 January - 2008 September (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Demonstration Project: Engineering the Resilience of Specific Nodal Complexes within Cities, 2006 September-October (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Janice E. Perlman – Mega-Cities Project Inc., 1993-2009 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Noel Kriftcher – Sustainability Modulus, 2009 May (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Jennifer Weeks – Megacities, 2009 January (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Green Buildings Workshop – Polytechnic Institute of NYU, 2009 January (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Seminar on Urban Challenges, 2010 February 5 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Macarthur Foundation, 2004 November - 2005 January (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Multidimensional Infrastructure Simulation Center – Polytechnic University, 2007 January (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Department of Homeland Security Transportation Security Meeting, 2007 March-April (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Faculty Seminar on Urban Challenges – Polytechnic Institute of NYU, 2009 November - 2010 January (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Faculty Seminar on Urban Challenges – Polytechnic Institute of NYU, 2010 February-April (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Saul Shapiro – New York City Economic Development Corp., 2007 February - 2008 March (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - B.S. in Sustainable Urban Environments – Polytechnic University, 2007 November (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - NYU-Poly's Urban Initiative, 2008 February - 2009 February (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Polytechnic University Urban Sustainability Courses, 2004-2005 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - City Innovation, 1995 May 15 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - "The Question of Sustainability and Diversity", 1997 March (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Sustainable Cities Notes, Undated (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Sustainability Moduli, 2007 September (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Jerry Hultin, 2008 January - 2009 September (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - Green Roofs Project, 2008 January-December (Box 46, Folder 27)
- Series V: Audio-Visual Material, 1985-2012
  This series contains audio and visual based materials, including VHS tapes, audiocassette tapes, CDs and DVDS, dating from 1987 to 2012. The VHS and audiocassette tapes primarily contain taped lectures from the Leadership Seminar Series run by George Bugliarello and lectures and speeches given by George Bugliarello in the classroom and in symposiums.
  - Subseries A: VHS Tapes, 1987-2001; 1995-1996
    - Leadership Seminar Series: David A. Conklin, Career Opportunities in Manufacturing, 1995 October 2 (Box 47, Cassette 1)
    - Leadership Seminar Series Eugene Fasulla The Role of Engineers in Rebuilding our Country, 1995 October 9 (Box 47, Cassette 2)
    - Leadership Seminar Series: Irene Van Slyke, How to Win Elections, 1995 October 30 (Box 47, Cassette 3)
    - Leadership Seminar Series: John S. Mayo, The Future of Telecommunications, 1995 November 6 (Box 47, Cassette 4)
    - Leadership Seminar Series: Frank Padavan, An Engineer's Career in State Government (2 copies), 1995 November 13 (Box 47, Cassette 5)
    - Leadership Seminar Series: Leadership Seminar Series: Robert D. Dalziel, International Telecommunications (2 copies), 1995 November 27 (Box 47, Cassette 6)
    - Leadership Seminar Series: Mel Horwitch, Business Management for the Twenty-First Century (2 copies), 1996 January 29 (Box 47, Cassette 7)
    - Leadership Seminar Series: Eleanor K. Baum Changing the Face of Engineering (2 copies), 1996 February 5 (Box 47, Cassette 8)
    - Leadership Seminar Series: Leonard Berkowitz A Lifetime of Learning in Exxon (2 copies), 1996 February 19 (Box 47, Cassette 9)
    - Leadership Seminar Series: John G. Puente International Satellite Communications (2 copies), 1996 February 26 (Box 47, Cassette 10)
    - Leadership Seminar Series: Anthony M. Johnson The Career of a Physicist in Industry and the University (Lasers and Ultrafast Optical Phenomena) (2 copies), 1996 March 4 (Box 47, Cassette 11)
    - Leadership Seminar Series: Dr. Shelley A. Harrison Building New High-Tech Companies (6 copies), 1996 March 11 (Box 47, Cassette 12)
    - Leadership Seminar Series: Jack M. Sipress Advances in International Communications Via Undersea Systems (3 copies), 1996 March 18 (Box 47, Cassette 13)
    - Leadership Seminar Series: Andrew Kalotay, Career Opportunities for Engineers in Finance (3 copies), 1996 March 25 (Box 47, Cassette 14)
    - Leadership Seminar Series: Jerome H. Lemelson: A Conversation with Jerome H. Lemelson Entrepreneur and Inventor Extraordinaire (2 copies), 1996 April 8 (Box 47, Cassette 15)
    - Leadership Seminar Series: William L. Friend, My Career in Engineering and Construction (3 copies), 1996 April 22 (Box 47, Cassette 16)
    - Leadership Seminar Series: James A. Dobkin, Engineering and the Practice of Law, 1996 September 30 (Box 47, Cassette 17)
    - Leadership Seminar Series: Dr. Gerhard Frohlich, Engineering and Engineering Management, 1996 October 21 (Box 47, Cassette 18)
    - Leadership Seminar Series: Craig G. Matthews, Your Career: Choices Not Made (2 copies), 1996 October 28 (Box 47, Cassette 19)
    - Leadership Seminar Series: Dr. William C.W. Mow, A System Engineer's Success in Merchandising, 1996 November 4 (Box 47, Cassette 20)
    - Leadership Seminar Series: Alexander V. d'Arbeloff The Art & The Science of Building A Company, 1996 November 18 (Box 47, Cassette 21)
    - Penn State – "Take Note" – Handling Technology Change, 1997 February 26 (Box 48, Cassette 1)
    - Workshop on Earth Systems, Engineering, October 4-6, 2001, University of Colorado, Tape 1, 2001 October 3-4 (Box 48, Cassette 2)
    - Workshop on Earth Systems, Engineering, October 4-6, 2001, University of Colorado, Tape 1- Part 2, 2001 October 3-4 (Box 48, Cassette 3)
    - Workshop on Earth Systems, Engineering, October 4-6, 2001, University of Colorado, Tape 2, 2001 October 5-6 (Box 48, Cassette 4)
    - Dr. George Bugliarello, "Knight Lines" Interview, "The Future of Man & Machine" (2 copies), 1996 October (Box 48, Cassette 5)
    - Educational Video Conferencing, TRT: 6:17, Undated (Box 48, Cassette 6)
    - Biology, Machines and Society, Dr. George Bugliarello, 1999 January 23 (Box 48, Cassette 7)
    - "Building Green" Audubon House-In Pursuit of Sustainable Architecture and Energy Efficiency, Undated (Box 48, Cassette 8)
    - Soros Tape (unlabeled, requires viewing), Undated (Box 48, Cassette 9)
    - Fire Department Conference, Tape 1, Undated (Box 48, Cassette 10)
    - Fire Department Conference, Tape 2, Undated (Box 48, Cassette 11)
    - Fire Department Conference, Tape 3, Undated (Box 48, Cassette 12)
    - The Automobile in America: A Socio-Technological View, Undated (Box 48, Cassette 13)
    - BEA White House Ceremony "Award of Medals of Science and Technology", Duplicated 8/11/88, Undated (Box 48, Cassette 14)
    - Soligen Presents: "Parts Now", Undated (Box 48, Cassette 15)
    - NIST Room Flashover Videos (FEMA), 2001 March (Box 48, Cassette 16)
    - The Healthcare Chaplaincy, "Excellence in Formation", 1998 November (Box 48, Cassette 17)
    - NIST Building & Fire Research Laboratory…Your Partner in Building, 1995 September (Box 48, Cassette 18)
    - The Search for Solutions: Investigation Evidence Patterns. Phillips Petroleum Company., 1987 (Box 48, Cassette 20)
    - Unnamed, undated VHS cassette with George Bugliarello business card attached (to be viewed) (Box 48, Cassette 19)
    - The Search for Solutions: Adaption Context Trial and Error. Phillips Petroleum Company, 1987 (Box 48, Cassette 21)
  - Subseries B: DVDs, 2002-2012
    - The National Academies Keck Futures Initiative, Smart Prosthetics Exploring Assistive Devices for The Body and Mind, 2008 September-November (Box 48, Disk 1)
    - "The Space Project", Barbara Confino, 2002 (Box 48, Disk 2)
    - Naval Research Laboratory, LCP, 12/04/2003,1. Fly Around Midtown, 2. Rock Center, 3. JPB Lecture (2 copies), 2003 December 4 (Box 48, Disk 3)
    - SRCES RAS Biomonitoring, 2007 (Box 48, Disk 4)
    - NESC Academy "Innovative Engineering Design" with Dr. Charles Camarda and Colleagues", Undated (Box 48, Disk 5)
    - Traffic Design: Traffic Control and Management Systems, Studio 37, 2005 December (Box 48, Disk 6)
    - Ten Years of Achievement: A Milestone in China's Modern Times, the 7th General Assembly and 10th Anniversary of the Chinese Academy of Engineering, June 2-5, 2004 (Chinese), 2004 June 2-5 (Box 48, Disk 7)
    - George Bugliarello Classroom Footage DVD-R (2 – 1/5/2012), 2012 January 5 (Box 48, Disk 8)
    - George Bugliarello, Rethinking Urbanization For Chemical Engineering - Power point presentation, Undated (Box 48, Disk 9)
    - MS&T'06 Materials Science & Technology - 2006 Conference and Exhibition - Conference Proceedings, 2006 October 15-19 (Box 48, Disk 10)
  - Subseries C: CDs, 1996-2007
    - Polytechnic, Vulnerability & Risk (Power Point), 2003 October 18 (Box 48, Disk 11)
    - Professor Jamiol Kowski, SNS Pisa (Scuola Normale Superiore), Undated (Box 48, Disk 12)
    - Proceedings, November 3-5, 2003, Washington DC Global Policy Summit on the Role of Performance-Based Building Regulations in Addressing Societal Expectations, International Policy, and Local Needs, 2003 November 3-5 (Box 48, Disk 13)
    - New York City Urban Security Initiative NYCUSI, Gray Hawk (Power Point), Undated (Box 48, Disk 14)
    - S. Klein Presentation, April 28, 2003 (Power Point), 2003 April 28 (Box 48, Disk 15)
    - S. Klein USI Presentation, 2003 July (Box 48, Disk 16)
    - OEM (Same as S. Klein USI Presentation), 2003 July 23 (Box 48, Disk 17)
    - LIFT 5/21/2003, S. Klein & G. Bugliarello "Engineering the Protection of our Cities" Power Point Presentation, 2003 May 21 (Box 48, Disk 18)
    - Physical & Cyber Security Awareness, Presented by US Secret Service, New York Electronic Crimes Task Force (2 copies), 2001 November 19 (Box 48, Disk 19)
    - FY08 Engineering Research & Technology Report, Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory – PDF document, Undated (Box 48, Disk 20)
    - George Bugliarello, Biomedical Engineering Specificity versus The Absolute, 4/20/2007 Revision, 2007 April 20 (Box 48, Disk 21)
    - Bugliarello Urban Sustainability: The Engineering Challenges (2 copies), 2007 February 21 (Box 48, Disk 22)
    - G. Bugliarello: Urban Sustainability Challenges, Paradigms, and Policies – Korea, 2007 October 10 (Box 48, Disk 23)
    - G. Bugliarello Urban Sustainability PPT, ASU, 2006 November 20 (Box 48, Disk 24)
    - ASU 18 / Arizona for Prof. Wener's Class, 11/17/2006, Urban Sustainability Challenges, 2006 November 17 (Box 48, Disk 25)
    - Humanity 3000 Energy Challenges, The Next Thousand Years: Executive Summary, Workshop Proceedings, Participants at Work, Bellevue, Washington USA, 2007 March 30 - April 1 (Box 48, Disk 26)
    - Bio-Terrorism Regional Preparedness, Russ Zajtchuk, M.D. Committee on Bio- Counter Terrorism, Undated (Box 48, Disk 27)
    - Unclassified, Information Assurance Technical Framework, September 2002, National Security Agency, 2002 September (Box 48, Disk 28)
    - George Bugliarello Oral History. Brooklyn Historical Society., 2007 (Box 48, Disk 29)
    - Power Point presentations - Chemical Engineering - Pictures, 2005 (Box 48, Disk 30)
    - Power Point presentations - National Academies - Georgetown, 2006 July 12 (Box 48, Disk 31)
    - Power Point presentations - Urban Sustainability - Arizona State University, 2006 February 10 (Box 48, Disk 32)
    - Power Point presentations - Urban Security Certificate Course; Chemical Engineering Recruiting presentation; Megacities; Publication list, 2003 October, 2004 September (Box 48, Disk 33)
    - Power Point presentations - Urban Engineering, 2004 November 22 (Box 48, Disk 34)
    - Power Point presentations - Megacities and the Challenges of their Rapid Growth: Poverty and Sustainability - Baltimore, 2004 October 18 (Box 48, Disk 35)
    - Power Point presentations - Sustainable Cities: Rethinking Urbanization; Megacities and the Challenges of their Rapid Growth: Poverty and Sustainability (Revised), 2004 October 18 (Box 48, Disk 36)
    - Power Point presentations - MetroTech - Intelligent Communities Forum 2005, 2005 June 8 (Box 48, Disk 37)
  - Subseries D: Audiocassette Tapes, 1985-2002
    - Polytechnic, Workshop on Technology in Merchandising & Distribution, Tape I, 1997 June 10 (Box 48, Cassette 1)
    - Polytechnic, Workshop on Technology in Merchandising & Distribution, Tape II, 1997 June 10 (Box 48, Cassette 2)
    - Polytechnic, Workshop on Technology in Merchandising & Distribution, Tape III, 1997 June 10 (Box 48, Cassette 3)
    - Polytechnic, Workshop on Technology in Merchandising & Distribution, Tape IV, 1997 June 10 (Box 48, Cassette 4)
    - Cybersecurity, LC 400, 2002 October 7 (Box 48, Cassette 5)
    - Bioterrorism, LC 400, 2002 October 7 (Box 48, Cassette 6)
    - October 7, 3rd Tape AM Session, 2002 October 7 (Box 48, Cassette 7)
    - October 7, 2nd Tape AM Session, 2002 October 7 (Box 48, Cassette 8)
    - October 7, 1st Tape AM Session, 2002 October 7 (Box 48, Cassette 9)
    - October 7, 2002, LC 102, 3-4:10pm, 2002 October 7 (Box 48, Cassette 10)
    - October 7, 2002, LC 102, 1:30-3:00pm, 2002 October 7 (Box 48, Cassette 11)
    - Lunch Speeches, Undated (Box 48, Cassette 12)
    - Computer & Soviet Security, 1986 April 4 (Box 48, Cassette 13)
    - George Bugliarello Remarks, ESE Symposium, Undated (Box 48, Cassette 14)
    - George Bugliarello: Religion in America Speech, Princeton Club, NYC, 1985 December 3 (Box 48, Cassette 15)
    - GB Port Washington LIBY Speech, 1990 May (Box 48, Cassette 16)
    - President's, Chem. Symposium, 1985 November 22 (Box 48, Cassette 17)
    - Speech Delivered at Rose-Human, Terre Haute, IN 47802 on Tuesday, September 3, 1991, 1991 September 3 (Box 48, Cassette 18)
    - Judy Carmichael, The Great Hall Gig (music cassette), Undated (Box 48, Cassette 19)
    - FireGround: Communications, Tracking and Information Management A Forum Series on Technology for Public Safety and Security, Thursday April 18, 2002. U.S.I., Tape 1 (2), 2002 April 18 (Box 48, Cassette 20)
    - FireGround: Communications, Tracking and Information Management A Forum Series on Technology for Public Safety and Security, Thursday April 18, 2002. U.S.I., Tape 2 (2), 2002 April 18 (Box 48, Cassette 21)
    - FireGround: Communications, Tracking and Information Management A Forum Series on Technology for Public Safety and Security, Thursday April 18, 2002. U.S.I., Tape 3 (2), 2002 April 18 (Box 48, Cassette 22)